Last Days in the Desert is a adventure, drama,
history film directed by Rodrigo García.
On his way out of the wilderness, Jesus struggles with the Devil over the fate
of a family in crisis, setting himself up for a dramatic test.
Jesus, played by Ewan McGregor.
Father, played by Ciarán Hinds.
Mother, played by Ayelet Zurer.
Son, played by Tye Sheridan.
Demonic Woman, played by Susan Gray.
Last Days in the Desert is a 2015 American drama film
written and directed by Rodrigo García.
A variation on the biblical story of the Temptation of Christ, the film stars Ewan McGregor in a dual role of Jesus (referred to in the film as "Yeshua")
and a demon who may or may not be Satan, while Tye Sheridan, Ciarán Hinds, and Ayelet Zurer play a family they meet while in the desert.
Last Days in the Desert premiered at the 2015 Sundance Film Festival on January
25, 2015 and was released in the United States on May 13, 2016.
The film explores themes of christianity, devil, desert, fasting, praying.
The tone is emotional.